You, Jonas.
Your fairies, the lot of you.
But, sir,
that's not I said leave.
Well, I've done it this time.
Anne.
Listen, I'm sorry about this. There's
nothing to apologize for.
You've done so much to help me.
It's not over yet.
We'll think of something.
We have to prove
that Sammy is at fault.
I guarantee you we won't
take this lying down.
All right then.
I'll see you tomorrow,
Keith. I look forward to it.
Miss Bridget.
Sounds like you're having
a tough time again.
Never knew there were so many rotten
apples attending the Radcliffe School.
Well,
you better show them a thing
or two tomorrow.
Thank you, ma'am. I'll try. The.
Jonas.
What an. You need something.
Thanks a lot for saving me.
It's fine.
I didn't do it for you.
I was scared, so I panicked.
Well, I'm.
Grateful either way.
I told you it wasn't about you.
Don't you remember?
I hate you an.
So have you figured
out what you're
going to do yet?
It's none of your business.
I picked out the motif
for my piece.
Keith complimented my sugar
confection today, getting
praise from someone so talented.
Of course I'm happy.
You were so excited.
If not for yesterday's events,
that might have been
a place where you belonged.
Yet having you here with me now
puts me at ease.
It's selfish, but shelf.
And shall we need to have
a talk? It's serious.
I told you I refused to listen
to your serious
questions any longer.
But wait, this time
it's actually something serious.
It's an silver sugar.
It's not right. Not right?
Yes, I was snacking on it. No,
I mean, I was just taste
testing it for quality.
And for some reason, the flavor and
texture weren't quite the same.
That's not
the sugar she refined. It's
the mass produced trash that the
Radcliffe Workshop was making.
Mithril lid pod.
Keep this secret from man.
Let her enter the contest tomorrow. And
don't dare breathe a word.
And what are you going to do?
Find her. Silver sugar.
Eliot! It's me. Open this door.
Can you come back later?
I'm kind of in the middle
of something.
The three of us can go
look for it.
To think that they would go
switch out the sugar barrels.
If I had to guess,
it would have to be.
Trust me.
I know what you're thinking.
But if it's true,
then we'll need some proof.
Which is why
we'll have to enlist
the help
of that loudmouth in there.
Come on out, Eliot.
It's in regards to Anne Halford.
Please don't say that.
Name right now, huh?
Anne. She is popular.
And Kat's here too.
Must be a mess, huh?
Lucky her to have so many
men fawning over her.
Clearly,
all that babying has gone to her
head.
Sounds like you know something.
Shel. You're here.
By the way. She's
gotten this far because she refuses to
stop trying no matter what.
If anyone's been baby'd,
it is you. Uh.
Great.
I worked so hard to console
her while she drank
away her heartbreak.
And you just undid all of it.
What do you want?
The silver sugar
that Anne refined. It seems
to have been switched out
with the workshops product.
Huh. But who would waste their time
on doing something so petty?
We have an idea.
But we need is the evidence.
Do you know where
we could find it?
Wait. Stop.
When you say the evidence,
do you mean you need
the sugar that Anne made?
Sorry, but I'm pretty
sure that's impossible now.
When you do something that's
bad, you destroy the evidence.
If I had done it, then I would
have thrown it away for sure.
Huh? Then how do we fix this?
I saw it. I saw it all.
I know what happened.
Who did it and where.
You can find
that girl's silver sugar
right now.
Is that true? Certainly.
Then tell me who's the culprit.
And where are the barrels?
I am not telling you anything.
I'm not so sure.
Mithra. Lid pod.
Is all that true? Huh?
Is what true?
You know that story
you told me about
Shel going into town
to get medicine for his hiccups?
Ah, yes. Fairies get hiccups on
occasion. Everyone knows that. Hmm.
What's wrong? Shel? Is there
something going on with you?
Sorry, Anne,
but we might be too late.
We just can't convince
her to talk. Huh?
Mr. Hingley and I came
to the exhibition,
but Charles stayed
behind to persuade her.
It's heartbreaking.
I could never have imagined
that our one chance to compete
would turn out this way.
Wait a minute, Keith. So she was
with you until you showed
up here. What's going on?
Did no one tell you, Mr. Keith
Powell?
Please stay at your table.
This morning I received
a note of questionable origin.
It says here.
Anne Halford, who plans
to compete in the sugar
confectionery exhibition,
is not worthy of bearing
the title Silver Sugar Master.
She lacks the skill necessary
to refine silver sugar.
You'll find proof of this in
the product she's brought today.
Inspect Halfords stock.
You'll find the mass
produced sugar that came
from this year's harvest.
That's a lie. With all due
respect, you're the Viscount.
You know her abilities
better than anyone.
May offer your opinion when
you've been asked Keith Powell.
The complaints been made,
which means we can't
ignore it without
facing further issues.
Sadly, you're right,
Miss Anne Harford. You
understand that we must
inspect your work.
Yes, of course sir. Please do.
For the sake of accountability.
I shouldn't
be the only
official to investigate it.
So Marcus Ratcliff is going
to examine it as well.
I'll remove the lid now.
Ha ha ha ha.
Mm.
There can be no doubt.
This is the mass
produced silver sugar
that was made at the main
Radcliffe workshop this year.
Are you sure? Mm.
Why?
Uh huh. Hey, there's the mail.
It might be something
from Mills Field.
I'll get it.
You stay. Have a nice
chat with your fairy friend.
All right. Bye.
I'll ask one more time.
Where's the silver sugar?
Answer me. If you refuse,
I'll cut you down.
That would be fine. She'd
never be a silver sugar master,
and you would be disposed of as
a fairy who killed a human.
And since I would want it that
way. It'd be a lover's suicide.
You want my wing?
Is that correct?
Yes I do.
Then if I give it to you,
will you tell me everything?
Yes.
Now talk. So it's in here.
Kiss me. Shall.
I'll tell you where
the silver sugar is hidden.
What's the meaning of this,
Harford? Please explain yourself.
I don't know. I swear I refined
my own silver sugar and I used
it to create my contest entry.
She did this
and she didn't find it herself.
And she doesn't
deserve to be here.
You impetuous idiots! I know
what it looks like, but she.
Was the one
who made a confection
for the former Duke of Felix.
I know this girl. There's no way
she can't refine her
own silver sugar.
Be silent, his Majesty, King Edmund
the Second is approaching.
What is all this?
Downing a scandal?
This girl again. I'm perplexed. Do
you enjoy causing constant turmoil?
I'm sorry, sire.
I didn't mean to.
I've heard the whole story.
The rules are quite clear.
Without silver sugar
that you refined for yourself,
you have no right to compete.
Oh, before you go,
let me inspect it
so it doesn't
qualify as an entry.
Even so. My queen desires it.
Exquisite. Ah.
Your Majesty. Is there a fairy
whose judgment you trust,
regardless of circumstance?
A fairy? Huh?
Come out! Clifford! Quickly!
We can always trust him.
Thank you. Sire.
An o. As a fairy, you can
tell quality sugar by its taste, right?
So if you tried this, you could
prove that I refined it well.
Now, please have a taste.
Are you certain? Yes. I hope
you like the flavor. Thank you.
Hmm'hmm. It's delicious. Quite.
This confection
was made from a high
quality silver sugar.
There's no way it's
a mass produced product.
But that's impossible.
She would go so far
as to destroy her own masterpiece
just to prove her innocence.
What matters is that I made this
piece for my own silver sugar.
That's what I want
everyone to know.
I realize that I've
disrupted the sugar
confectionery exhibition two times now,
and I deeply apologize.
Are quite important. Miss Bridget. This is
the daughter of Glen page,
head of the Page
Workshop Schools.
She says there's something
she needs us to know. Proceed.
My name is Bridget Page, sire.
I am deeply honored.
Speak your peace. Your Majesty.
I am acquainted with this girl.
I can testify
to the whereabouts of
the silver sugar
that she refined. Are.
Oh, well, in that case,
where is it?
It's in there. Inside that tent, you'll
find barrels labeled Sammy Jones,
but the silver sugar inside them was
not refined by Sammy himself,
because an Helford
made every bit of it.
That can't be. I'm sorry,
Sammy, but I saw everything.
You gathered up your
cohorts and quietly
took the barrels
from Ann's cart.
I wasn't going to report it,
but things have changed.
No, the Paige school is making
a false accusation.
It's a vicious lie.
Tell them, Sammy.
That bring the barrels.
Out to us immediately.
Hmm. It tastes the same.
The contents
are without doubt the work
of an Halford.
You've switched
out the silver sugar, Sammy.
How could you do something
so reckless? I'm sorry.
Headmaster. Please forgive me. Of all times
you would do that now?
The silver sugar.
I just thought that everything
would be better if I could
say that I had made it.
Curse you! You fool,
you little worm!
Well, I guess it's not uncommon for
sugar artisans to play dirty.
I can't apologize enough for this
disgraceful behavior, Your Majesty.
As headmaster of the school,
I will
take full responsibility
for punishing him.
I can assure you of that.
So please have mercy.
Silence! Leave my sight. But, Downing, let
us proceed. Sire and Halford,
your words were true.
You've brought your
peace and your silver sugar,
so I won't dismiss you.
Thank you. Sire.
Miss Bridget, thanks so much.
There's no need to thank me.
I've been rewarded.
This year's sugar confectionery
exhibition will now begin.
Today, we will determine
the greatest artisan
in the kingdom
and grant him or her
the title of Silver
Sugar Master Citizens.
The sugar confections will
now be inspected by His Majesty.
Huh? What a powerful
yet elegant fairy.
If anything could truly be flawless,
it would be this piece.
I've never seen
a sugar confection that gave
form to its
subjects so effectively.
Tell me then,
who is this craftsman?
That's Keith Powell, sir.
The son of
Edward, our previous
silver sugar viscount.
I see. Impressive.
Well, Keith Powell. Sire.
You take after your father.
Yes. His
influence is clear in your work.
As a faithful imitation
of our world. This is perfect.
Unfortunately, imitation
is not always seeking a.
I see. So that was why, no.
Matter how detailed,
nothing crafted by humans
can ever compare
to the beauty of the real thing.
Anne Halford Sugar Confection,
for instance, depicts
a fairy wing woven together
with climbing roses.
She's given form
to something that can
only be described as a vision.
Even the slight damage
from the flower
she broke off is somehow
still beautiful to me.
I understand, sire.
I'm proud to decree
that this Miss Anne
Halford sugar confection
will hereby be awarded
this year's Royal Medal.
We will henceforth recognize
her as a silver sugar master.
You get. Oh. Come on.
His Majesty is waiting for you.
I really wanted a Royal Medal.
Well. Shall we?
Silver sugar master. For
today and all
the rest of your days.
Live in reverence
of this sacred art.
She de Jesus. Nena e. Mamma.
Yes, Your.
Majesty, I will devote the rest
of my life to sugar confections.
I was an idiot. I spent too
much time worrying about you.
But next year, I'll be
the one to receive the medal.
When I do, let's compete again.
And by the way, Keith. Mm.
Thank you so much.
I was able to keep on trying
because you supported me.
I'm flattered, but you're
thanking the wrong person.
Chow's the one who
convinced Brigitte to help.
So why don't you go and show
him your new medal?
Till next time, Keith. Goodbye.
So I
won. They gave me the medal.
You've taken hold of your destiny. So.
You don't need me, huh?
Wait a second.
What are you talking about?
I have to leave you now.
I don't understand.
Did you get tired
of being around me or something?
Tell me,
what's the matter with you?
I didn't want to let go.
But why?
Well, that's no good. A pretty
girl shouldn't be sitting in the
street. You'll ruin your dress.
Mr. Collins. It must be
painful not knowing the why.
No. So, since I'm the ally
of all women, I'll explain it.
Your fairy friend in order to determine
where your silver sugar was.
He had to give
his wing to Bridget.
His wing? He sold his freedom to
make sure you'd be all right.
No, please don't go.
You can't do this. Wait!
Show. Stop! I don't
want us to be apart.
Sherm.